<ModMetaData>
	<name>SpiceMelange</name>
	<author>Between The Borders</author>
    <packageId>BetweenTheBorders.SpiceMelange</packageId>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.1</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<description>
Spice blows, harvesting, and refining.\n\n

This is a testing release, but should be playable as-is. There has been no balance pass, and there is no promise Spice won't be too common or too rare.\n\n

Current benefits include psychic power bonues at higher levels, and until I figure out how much is reliant on Royalty, it is listed as a dependency.\n\n

Spice blows occur randomly, and the pre-spice mass must be dried either in an autoclave (same tech and image as the vanilla drug lab) or in a temperature of above 25C. Effects of withdrawal are not well tailored. It will take many doses to get to higher status effects.\n\n

Current effects include increased stats, psychic powers, immunity to common diseases, and cosmetic bluing of the eyes. These kick in at different levels of severity.\n\n

There's a lot to be done, but I wanted feedback on mechanisms and balance. It's been a trip figuring out things so far, and hopefully I figure out HugsLib to allow for user configuration, but I wanted to get feedback on systems ASAP.\n\n
\n\n

Thanks for all the support!\n\n

All RimWorld mod sources uploaded to https://github.com/faragher/ (but it may take a while after release)\n\n


Dune and all its related IPs are, of course, property of Frank Herbert, his descendants and licensees. No infringement intended, etc.


</description>
	<url>https://steamcommunity.com/id/Between The Borders/myworkshopfiles/?appid=294100</url>
		<modDependencies>
	    <li>
	      <packageId>Ludeon.Rimworld.Royalty</packageId>
	      <displayName>Royalty DLC</displayName>
	      <downloadUrl>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1149640/RimWorld__Royalty/</downloadUrl>
	      <steamWorkshopUrl>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1149640/RimWorld__Royalty/</steamWorkshopUrl>
	    </li>
	</modDependencies>
</ModMetaData>


